levitra.com 2009-06-20

# Privacy Statement: LEVITRA.com

Privacy Statement

BAYER, GSK, and Schering-Plough Corporation respect the privacy of visitors to the LEVITRA Web site. This Web site endeavors to collect, maintain, and secure your personal information in accordance with the principles described within this policy. This policy applies only to the information collected on this Web site. This privacy policy does not apply to information collected offline. Information collected online from other Web sites operated by BAYER, GSK, or Schering-Plough are governed by the privacy statements that appear on those sites. 

**Data We Collect**

BAYER, GSK, and Schering-Plough will only collect personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address, that you provide or that is provided to us with your permission. Portions of this Web site may not ask you to supply your personal information, allowing you to visit our site without telling us who you are. However, some areas or services may require you to provide personal information in order to receive promotional offers. When you register with us, you may need to complete certain fields (some are required and some are optional). In this instance, if you choose to withhold any personally identifiable information required by us, it will not be possible for you to obtain the promotional offers. 

In addition, BAYER, GSK, or Schering-Plough may collect non-personally identifiable information about how you use our Web sites using analysis technologies. These analysis technologies may be provided by third parties. Information that might be collected using these technologies includes, for example, the pages you visit on our site, the paths you take within our sites, and the length of time that you spend on our Web sites. We use this information in the aggregate in order to better understand how to improve the quality of our Web sites. 

**How We Use and Disclose Your Information**

BAYER, GSK, and Schering-Plough and/or the companies we hire will use this information to comply with your request for information, to contact you in connection with the promotion of LEVITRA, to better understand your needs and how we can improve our products and services, or as otherwise disclosed to you on the Web page when you submit your information to us. We will not sell or otherwise transfer the personally identifiable information you provide to us at this Web site to any third parties for their own use without your permission. 

**Opt Out**

You may stop receiving future communications about LEVITRA that are initiated by BAYER, GSK, or Schering-Plough, at any time. To cancel these further communications, please complete the following form: **[LEVITRA.com Opt-out](https://www.levitra.com/optout/opt_out.jsp)**. From time to time, this site may allow visitors to the site to send "e-card" communications or messages that refer friends to the site. Because the site does not collect or retain the e-mail addresses of the recipients of these types of messages, opt-out from these communications is not possible. If you have any concerns or questions regarding these messages, please contact the Customer Response Center at 1-888-825-5249. 

**Cookies and Internet Tags**

Like many Web sites, this Web site uses a technology called "cookies". A cookie is a small text file that a Web server gives your browser to store on your computer when you access a Web site. Cookies are capable of storing many types of data and may be placed on your browser by BAYER, GSK, and Schering-Plough or by a third party. Cookies may be used for a variety of purposes on this Web site: 

—This site sets cookies that keep you from having to enter a password more than once during visits to one or more of our sites. 

—We also use cookies to help us analyze usage of our sites and traffic among our sites more accurately and to provide you with information of interest to you. For example, cookies are used on this site to record the total number of hits received on the site and Web pages. 

—Cookies also allow BAYER, GSK, and Schering-Plough to determine whether you came to this site from another BAYER, GSK, and Schering-Plough site or from an advertising banner or link on a non-BAYER, GSK, and Schering-Plough Web site, so that we can, for example, measure the effectiveness of the links among our sites and the effectiveness of our advertising on non-BAYER, GSK, or Schering-Plough Web sites. 

—Similarly, cookies allow us to determine whether you register on or visit any of our Web sites, which enables us to analyze how particular users use our sites and whether registered and unregistered users of our Web sites use our sites differently. 

—Cookies also allow us to maintain information about how particular visitors use our family of sites, which enables us to better provide such visitors with information relevant to their interests. This may include using information about your use of our sites in conjunction with personally identifiable information that you have volunteered to us on one of our sites. 

This is not an exhaustive list of all uses of cookies on this Web site. In all cases in which cookies are used, however, neither BAYER, GSK, Schering-Plough, nor any third party will use the cookie to collect personally identifiable information from our site unless you voluntarily agree to enter the information. Most web browsers are set up to accept cookies. You can, however, reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Note, however, that some portions of our sites may not work properly if you refuse cookies. 

Some BAYER, GSK, or Schering-Plough websites use a third-party advertising service to display advertising on other, non-BAYER, GSK, or Schering-Plough Web sites. In addition to placing advertisements on certain non-BAYER, GSK, or Schering-Plough Web pages, these services may also place a segment of code called a clear pixel tag, also known as a "GIF", on certain BAYER, GSK, and Schering-Plough Web pages for the purpose of measuring the effectiveness of advertisements in bringing visitors to our Web sites. GIFs may also be used with cookies to track the total number of visitors to our Web site, the number of visitors to various Web pages, and the domain names of our visitors' Internet service providers. No personally identifiable information is collected in this process. 

As is common among Internet site operators, BAYER, GSK, and Schering-Plough Web sites maintain web server logs. Web servers automatically identify your computer by its IP address and collect that information in its web server logs. BAYER, GSK, and Schering-Plough web server logs collect statistical data that is generated by your computer when it visits a BAYER, GSK, and Schering-Plough Web site, such as the type of web browser (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer) and operating system (Windows 95 or Mac OS) used to access the site, the domain name of your Internet service provider, the date and time you access our site, and the pages you visit. BAYER, GSK, and Schering-Plough Web sites use this non-personally identifying web server log information for a variety of purposes. Some of these purposes include: system administration; to examine overall traffic trends on our sites; trouble-shooting; and to gather broad demographic information about users of our sites. No personally identifiable information is contained in these web server logs. 

**Confidentiality**

You should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever completely secure or error-free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from this site may not be secure and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail. Moreover, where you use passwords, ID numbers, or other special access features on this site, it is your responsibility to safeguard them. 

**Security**

BAYER, GSK, and Schering-Plough use reasonable and appropriate physical, technical, and administrative security safeguards in order to protect your data from coincidental or deliberate manipulation, loss, destruction, or access by unauthorized persons. As part of the collection and processing of personal data, all transferred information will be encrypted to prevent misuse of the data by third parties. Our security procedures are reviewed on a regular basis. 

**Personal Information and Children**

This BAYER, GSK, and Schering-Plough Web site is not intended or designed to attract children under the age of 13. We will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from any person under the age of 13. 

As a convenience to our visitors, BAYER, GSK, and Schering-Plough's sites currently contain links to a number of Web sites that we believe may offer useful information. The privacy policy and provisions described here do not apply to those sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their data collection and distribution policies. 

**International Policy**

This Web site is intended for access and use by U.S. residents only and is subject to all applicable U.S. laws. 

**Changes to our Privacy Statement**

From time to time, BAYER, GSK, and Schering-Plough may decide to modify their practices and policies, and we reserve the right to revise this BAYER, GSK, and Schering-Plough Internet Privacy Statement as necessary to disclose such changes in our practices and policies. Any such changes to this BAYER, GSK, and Schering-Plough Internet Privacy Statement will be promptly communicated on this page. Any information that you submit before the change in policy will be used by BAYER, GSK, and Schering-Plough and/or the companies we hire in a manner that is consistent with the BAYER, GSK, and Schering-Plough Internet Privacy Statement in effect at the time you submitted your information. Continued use of our sites after receiving notice of a change in our privacy statement shall indicate your consent to the use of newly-submitted information in accordance with the changed, amended, or updated BAYER, GSK, and Schering-Plough Internet Privacy Statement. 

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding the use of your personal information obtained on the LEVITRA Web site, you can contact the Customer Response Center at 1-888-825-5249. We will use reasonable efforts to promptly respond to any requests, questions, or concerns you may have regarding the use of your personal information. 

This privacy policy is effective as of February 2, 2006. By using this site, you signify your assent to this Privacy Statement. 

Back to Top
